bulldogreporter.com 2019-04-30

# Privacy Policy - Agility PR Solutions

At Agility PR Solutions we understand the importance of your privacy. This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for the Agility PR Solutions website ([agilitypr.com](https://agilitypr.com/)), all other internet properties and subdomains (collectively the “Web Sites”) belonging to Agility PR Solutions or any of its Affiliates (the “Company”, “us” or “we”), and the Company’s subscription products (collectively, the “Services”). Each time you access or use the Web Sites or the Services you agree to this Privacy Statement in its entirety.

“Affiliate” means a legal entity that controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with the Company, but only while that control relationship exists; “control” means the direct or indirect ownership or control of 50% or more of the stock or other equity interest entitled to vote for the election of directors or equivalent governing body.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Passive and Active Collection**. When you visit our Web Sites we collect and keep track of certain information that is not readily personally identifiable, such as the domains from which people visit us, IP addresses and other anonymous statistical data involving your use of the Web Sites and our Services. There are also times when we may need information from you, such as your name and address contact details and payment information in connection with providing you certain Services. For example, in order to access our software-as-a-service products, we need to collect and maintain user names and email addresses to manage login authentication and to otherwise manage your user experience. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Web Sites or in connection with the Services.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**. There are various technologies, including one called “cookies”, which are used by us and our Affiliates to analyze trends and gather statistical data about our users. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can control the use of cookies via your individual browser, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Web Sites, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Web Sites may be limited.

## WHAT WE DO WITH INFORMATION WE COLLECT

If you provide us with personal information, we will use that information as intended by you or as permitted by law. For instance, we will use personal information provided as part of the subscription process to our Services, to provide our Services to you, to personalize your experience with us, to keep you informed of our products and Services that may be of interest to you, and to reach you when necessary regarding issues concerning your use of our Services. We also use your IP address for information technology support, to administer our Services, and to gather demographic information. We may aggregate the information we collect (including your personal information) for trends and statistical purposes. We reserve the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate data about our Web Site users and users of our Services for lawful purposes.

## HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Statement or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. We may share your personal information with our Affiliates. We also sometimes hire other companies to provide certain business-related functions (“Service Providers”). These Service Providers have access to personal information as necessary to provide their respective services to us.

We also may disclose personal information: (a) in response to a lawful request by public authorities, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; (b) under a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request; (c) in connection with a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event (in this case, personal information may be a part of assets transferred from our company to the acquiring company); and (d) to any third-party as set forth herein or with your prior consent to do so.

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The Web Sites may contain links to other websites. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policy. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

## PRIVACY AND SECURITY

We have implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational procedures to maintain the security of the information we retain. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free so please keep this in mind when deciding what information to send to us.

## DATA RETENTION

We will retain your personal information for as long as we have a relationship with you.  Once the relationship ends, we will retain the personal information to maintain business and financial records; to comply with legal requirements; to resolve disputes; to manage our agreements, such as for billing and collection; and to continue to communicate with you. We will delete your personal information when it is no longer required for these or other purposes.

## INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

The Company operates globally so it is necessary to transfer your information internationally. If personal information is transferred from the European Economic Area to a country that has not received a decision of adequacy from the European Commission, the personal information will be transferred using the European Commission approved Standard Contractual Clauses or the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework. Agility PR Solution LLC is a participant in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, and its Privacy Shield Privacy Statement can be found [here](http://innodata.com/privacy-shield/). Irrespective of which country you reside in or supply information from, you authorize the Company to use your information in any country where the Company operates. By using the Web Sites or the Services you consent to your information being collected, used and transferred as set forth in this Privacy Statement.

## MINORS

Visitors under 18 years of age are not permitted to use the Services /or submit their personal information at any Web Site. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under 18 years of age.

## YOUR RIGHTS OVER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You have certain rights regarding your personal information, subject to local law. Under the EU data protection laws these rights include the right to ask us to delete or erase your personal data, the right to ask us to amend or rectify your personal information, the right to object to our use of your personal information, the right to restrict our processing of your personal information, the right of access to your personal information, and the right of portability of your personal data in a machine-readable format.

Some of these rights only apply in certain circumstances. To exercise or discuss any of these rights please contact us as set forth in the “Questions” section below. We will make a sincere effort to respond to such requests in a timely manner. We may need to verify your identity before granting access to personal information in our custody and control.

The data controller of the information collected through the Web Sites is Agility PR Solutions Limited, Tayfield House, c/o ASFB, Poole Road, Bournemouth, England, BH4 9DW ([legal@agilitypr.com](mailto:legal@agilitypr.com)).  For Services provided by Agility PR Solutions the data controller is the contracting Agility PR Solutions company indicated with the company’s address on the applicable order form.

## **QUESTIONS**

Questions, requests, comments or complaints regarding this Privacy Statement or the privacy practices of Company generally can be emailed to: [legal@agilitypr.com](mailto:legal@agilitypr.com).

We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint or concern about privacy. If, however, you believe that we have not been able to assist with your complaint or concern, you have the right to make a complaint to the data protection authority.

## CHANGES

We will update this Privacy Statement from time to time. Any changes will be posted on this page with an updated revision date.

**Last Updated: June 28, 2018**
